[
  {
  "id": 1,
  "question": "fiets",
  "answer": "bicycle"
},
{
  "id": 2,
"question": "patat",
"answer": "chips"
},
  {
    "id": 3,
    "question": "stoplicht",
    "answer": "traffic light"
  },
  {
    "id": 4,
    "question": "woordenboek",
    "answer": "dictionary"
  },
  {
    "id": 5,
    "question": "kasteel",
    "answer": "castle"
  },
  {
    "id": 6,
    "question": "koekje",
    "answer": "cookie"
  },
  {
    "id": 7,
    "question": "vuurtoren",
    "answer": "lighthouse"
  },
  {
    "id": 8,
    "question": "bos",
    "answer": "forest"
  },
  {
  "id": 9,
  "question": "speeltuin",
  "answer": "playground"
  },
  {
    "id": 10,
    "question": "lepel",
    "answer": "spoon"
  },
  {
    "id": 11,
    "question": "kast",
    "answer": "closet"
  },
  {
    "id": 12,
    "question": "bankstel",
    "answer": "couch"
  },
  {
    "id": 13,
    "question": "rotonde",
    "answer": "roundabout"
  },
  {
    "id": 14,
    "question": "brug",
    "answer": "bridge"
  },
  {
    "id": 15,
    "question": "kinderen",
    "answer": "children"
  },
  {
    "id": 16,
    "question": "vlinder",
    "answer": "butterfly"
  },
  {
    "id": 17,
    "question": "speelgoed",
    "answer": "toys"
  },
  {
    "id": 18,
    "question": "toetsenbord",
    "answer": "keyboard"
  },
  {
    "id": 19,
    "question": "schildpad",
    "answer": "turtle"
  },
  {
    "id": 20,
    "question": "kaas",
    "answer": "cheese"
  },
  {
    "id": 21,
    "question": "eiland",
    "answer": "island"
  },
  {
    "id": 22,
    "question": "deurbel",
    "answer": "doorbell"
  },
  {
    "id": 23,
    "question": "film",
    "answer": "movie"
  },
  {
    "id": 24,
    "question": "steelpan",
    "answer": "saucepan"
  },
  {
    "id": 25,
    "question": "kippen",
    "answer": "chickens"
  },
  {
    "id": 26,
    "question": "kleuter",
    "answer": "toddler"
  },
  {
    "id": 27,
    "question": "oma",
    "answer": "grandmother"
  },
  {
    "id": 28,
    "question": "kapper",
    "answer": "barber"
  },
  {
    "id": 29,
    "tools": "gereedschap",
    "answer": "barber"
  },
  {
    "id": 30,
    "tools": "kersentaart",
    "answer": "cherrypie"
  }
]













